bakchodbilli.in 2015-06-08

# Privacy Policy - Bakchod Billi Official

## Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to Bakchodbilli.in. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Bakchodbilli.in collects, and the ways in which Bakchodbilli.in uses that personal information. Personal information collection Bakchodbilli.in may collect and use the following kinds of personal information: information about your use of this website. information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website. information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services. Using personal information Bakchodbilli.in may use your personal information to: administer this website personalize the website for you Where Bakchodbilli.in discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement. In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, [NAME] may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights. Securing your data Bakchodbilli.in will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Cross-border data transfers Information that Bakchodbilli.in collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which Bakchodbilli.in operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy. You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information. Updating this statement Bakchodbilli.in may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes. Other websites This website may contains links to other websites. Bakchodbilli.in is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party. Contact If you have any questions about this privacy policy or Bakchodbilli.in treatment of your personal information, please write: by email to info@bakchodbilli.in
